A Guide to the Tazewell family papers, 1623-1930
Library of Virginia
- 30 September 1863 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  abstract of articles purchased at Hillsboro in the quarter ending 30 September 1863 by Major Edmund Bradford controlling QM, NC
- 30 September 1863 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  account and receipt-H. D. Turner-NC map, army regulations
- 12 October 1863 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  receipt from A. A. Wilbon to Anne Bradford for payment for beds and chairs
- 28 October 1863 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  receipt from Henry Scott to Anne E. Bradford for payment for beef
- 30 October 1863 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  receipt from E. D. Guthrie to Anne E. Bradford for feather bed and other items
- 2 November 1863 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  receipt for 2 sides calf uppers[?] and salt-Hugh Blair Grigsby to Mrs. Bradford
- 4 November 1863 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  receipt from Rodenbarger [?] and Company for pot and skillet-Major Bradford in Danville
- 18 November 1863 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  receipt from William O. Bouldin to Major Bradford-beef and mutton
- 23 November 1863 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  receipt from William O. Bouldin to Major Bradford for purchase of beef from George C. Smith
- December 1863 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  receipt from Charlotte Travis to Sally Tazewell for payment for weaving
- 3 December 1863 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  receipt from H. A. Woods to Bradford for payment for hauling wood
- 4 December 1863 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  account Edmund Bradford with W. O. Bouldin-paid
- 7 December 1863 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  receipt from J. W. Daniel to Hugh Blair Grigsby
- 18 December 1863 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  receipt for city tax paid by estate of Littleton Waller Tazewell
- 25 December 1863 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  receipt from James Scott to Edmund Bradford-for Irish potatoes
- 29 December 1863 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  D. F. Morton receipt to Hugh Blair Grigsby-purchase of bacona
- 31 December 1863 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  bond from Hugh Blair Grigsby and Edmund Bradford to William T. and James Scott, committee for Sarah E. Read-hire of a slave
- January 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  account of Edmund Bradford with Hugh Blair Grigsby for meal, salt, etc.-paid
- 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  state tax-Littleton Waller Tazewell estate
- 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  state tax-Sally N. Tazewell
- 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  state tax-John, Sally, and Ella Tazewell
- 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  receipt from A. R. Watkins to Edmund Bradford for tailoring job by M. A. Williamson for pants and collars
- 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  receipt from M. A. Williamson to Edmund Bradford for payment for tailoring
- 1 January 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  receipt for payment from the Misses Tazewell for pew rent at Christ Church
- 8 January 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  receipt of items from Captain J. J. Waggoner consigned to Major Edmund Bradford
- 8 January 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  account Major Edmund Bradford with Captain J. J. Waggoner
- 13 January 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  bill from William Grieve to John N. Tazewell for making coat, pants, and vest-asks him to pay Mrs. Waller since Grieve owes her rent
- 1 February 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  account for Miss Tazewell-milk
- February 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  receipt from M. A. Norris to Sally Tazewell-payment for milk
- 1 February 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  received of Major Bradford $1025 in payment for mare-Samuel T. Barnes
- 1 February 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  agreement between Edward P. Wescoat for Sally Tazewell and Peter Tazewell for Peter's services on Old Plantation
- 1 February 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  agreement between Edward P. Wescoat for Sally Tazewell and Leah Tazewell for Peter's services on King's Creek
- 18 February 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  receipt from William H. Millner to Edmund Bradford for payment for 3 wagons for one day and hire of one hand
- March 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- March 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  receipt to Sally Tazewell for purchase of clams
- 4 March 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  Tazewell Taylor [?] to Ella Tazewell-will try to track down accounts
- April 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- 16 April 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  receipt from L. F. Cropper to Sally Tazewell for payment for barrel of flour
- 21 April 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  receipt from George C. Orgain to Edmund Bradford
- 26 April 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  receipt from William Nichols and Company for payment
- 29 April 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  receipt from Samuel Kirk and Sons, Baltimore-six silver table spoons and six silver tea spoons-Mrs. Irwin[?]
- 1 May 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  receipt from L. F. Cropper to Sally Tazewell for payment for milk
- 3 May 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  account and receipt-Sally Tazewell with Mary Nottingham-services to negro woman Jinney
- 4 May 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  payment to Jupiter White for hauling cord of wood
- 4 May 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  Mrs. Waller payment to Jupiter White for hauling cord of wood-receipt
- June 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- 1 June 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  receipt from W. R. Norris to Sally Tazewell-payment for milk
- 4 June 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  receipt from Bocock and Parish to Bradford for payment for lime
- 8 June 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  receipt from William B. Tyson grocer to Mrs. Davidson
- 11 June 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  receipt from Jupiter White for payment for hauling cord of wood
- 16 June 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  receipt from the United States Internal Revenue for payment of taxes on property in Northampton County by John N. Tazewell
- 30 June 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  receipt from Jupiter White for payment for hauling a cord of wood
- July 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- 1 July 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- 3 July 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  Edward P. Wescoat, agent for Sally Tazewell agreement with Frank Means for labor at Old Plantation
- 3 July 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  receipt from W. R. Hudgins, Norfolk to Miss Tazewell-hooks
- 7 July 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  receipt from Ethan Allen to Mary Waller
- 19 July 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  receipt from Kimberly Brothers of Norfolk to John N. Tazewell
- 19 July 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- 27 July 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  receipt from A. A. Gwathney to Miss Tazewell in payment for repair of chair
- August 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- 12 August 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  receipt for coffee from E. Vance grocer to John N. Tazewell
- 13 August 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- 18 August 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  E. M. Rodman to John N. Tazewell-selling an afghan to help a church raise money
- 22 August 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- 24 August 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  receipt from L. Salusbury to Miss Tazewell for payment for bedstead
- 25 August 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  receipt from Charles S. Holt to Miss Tazewell for payment
- 27 August 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  receipt and receipt from H. W. Presby and Co. to Captain Chamberlain for whiskey and brandy
- 27 August 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  receipt and receipt from Seldner and Company, Norfolk to Sarah (Sallie) Tazewell
- September 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- 9 September 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- 15 September 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  receipt from W. E. Holt to Major Edmund Bradford for payment made by Captain C. R. King
- 17 September 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  United States Internal Revenue payment of excise tax on silver plate by Ella Tazewell
- 17 September 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  United States Internal Revenue payment of excise tax on silver plate by John N. Tazewell
- 17 September 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  United States Internal Revenue payment of excise tax on silver plate by Sally Tazewell
- October 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- 6 October 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  receipt from William Grieve to John N. Tazewell for payment for tailoring
- 14 October 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  receipt from L. Salusbury to Sally Tazewell for payment for coal
- 19 October 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  account with Charles Conick-wood and drayage
- 19 October 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  receipt from W. F. Allen, grocer to John N. Tazewell
- 20 October 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  receipt to Sally Tazewell from Robert B. Tunstall for vaccination and visits to Milly
- 20 October 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  receipt to John N. Tazewell from Robert B. Tunstall for payment for vaccination, advice, and visits
- 20 October 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  receipt to Ella Tazewell from Robert B. Tunstall for vaccination and visits
- 21 October 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  receipt from the New York Daily News to Mary T. Waller for payment for subscription
- 25 October 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  United States receipt for direct taxes-(estate of) Littleton Waller Tazewell
- 25 October 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- 26 October 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  receipt to Miss Tazewell from W. F. Allen grocer for flour
- November 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- 3 November 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  account of Sally Tazewell with John Feast and Son-paid
- 3 November 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  account of Sally Tazewell with George L. Crow-paid
- 9 November 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  receipt to Miss Tazewell from E. C. Deming grocers
- 11 November 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  receipt from Baltimore Steam Packet Company to Tazewell Taylor for freight for Miss Tazewell payment
- 18 November 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  receipt from William A. Thom to Edmund Bradford for payment of $100 for board
- December 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  Mary T. Waller-payment of city taxes
- December 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  Sally Tazewell-payment of city taxes
- December 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  John N., Sallie, and Ella Tazewell-payment of city taxes
- December 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  memorandum on city taxes for December 1864
- 14 December 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  receipt from William M. Watkins to Edmund Bradford for $625 for payment for corn at government prices
- 17 December 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  receipt from Thomas S.L.L. Nottingham to Sally Tazewell for payment
- 20 December 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  note by Luke Tazewell for payment in full satisfying agreement between Edward P. Wescoat agent for Sally Tazewell and Luke Tazewell for work on Old Plantation
- 24 December 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  receipt from William Nichols and Company for potatoes-paid
- 26 December 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  receipt from S. E. Mayhew to Sally Tazewell for payment for milk
- 29 December 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  receipt from W. F. Allen grocers, etc. to Sally Tazewell-apples
- 29 December 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  receipt from Kate Richardson for payment for tuition for sons Sidney and Eddie
- 30 December 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  receipt from W. F. Allen grocers, etc. to Sally Tazewell-bacon
- 31 December 1864 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  receipt from the state of Virginia to Edmund Bradford for payment of soldiers tax
- 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  Anne E. Bradford to Captain O. Brown, superintendent Negro Affairs-she owns farm in Princess Ann County currently occupied by Superintendent-asks for return of property which was left to her by her father LWT
- 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  memorandum on taxes paid by the Tazewells in 1865
- 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  monies received and expended by Sally Tazewell
- 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  Edmund Bradford in accounts current with Sally Tazewell
- 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  envelope-Major Bradford-concerning private money matters during the war-empty
- 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  receipt for payment of the lamp tax in Norfolk
- 1 January 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  Misses Tazewell-pew rental Christ Church
- 1 January 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  receipt from the New York Albion to Sarah (Sallie) Tazewell for subscription
- 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  list of rents paid
- 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  receipt from M. A. Norris for dress work for Sallie and Ella Tazewell-paid
- 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  receipt from J. J. Sturdivant to Sally Tazewell for payment
- 17 January 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  receipt from George Sangster, dealer in spirtuous and malt liquors, Portsmouth, to John N. Tazewell for ale and delivery-paid
- 24 January 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  F. T. Berry receipt to Major Bradford
- 7 February 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  receipt from B. W. Gatch to Sally Tazewell for payment for glass and putty
- 10 February 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  receipt from Kimberly Brothers to John N. Tazewell for chees-paid
- 13 February 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  receipt from George Sangster, dealer in liquor
- 18 February 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  receipt to John Tazewell from Jacob Riddick, barber
- 2 March 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  receipt from Eggleston and Brother to Major Bradford for payment
- 4 March 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  receipt from William B. Tyson, grocer, to Mrs. Smith
- 17 March 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  receipt from Jupiter White for payment of hauling cord of wood
- 21 March 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  receipt from Samuel Feast and Sons, florists to Sally Tazewell-paid
- 23 March 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  account of John N. Tazewell with Bolsom and Moore-paid
- 31 March 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  United States receipt for direct taxes-John N. Tazewell
- 31 March 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  Mrs. M. P. Waller to Norfolk post office-rent and newspaper postage
- 1 April 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  receipt from Charles S. Holt to Miss Tazewell for payment for material
- April 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  receipt from Scott for payment for cord of wood and drayage
- April 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  receipt from Mutual assurance Society against Fire on Buildings of the State of Virginia-John N., Sallie, and Ella Tazewell
- April 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  receipt from Mutual assurance Society against Fire on Buildings of the State of Virginia-M. P. Waller and wife
- 1 April 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  receipt from Charles A. Smith to Miss Tazewell-for sheeting and drilling
- 4 April 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  receipt from Charles A. Smith for payment for material-dress goods, calico, handkerchief, hose, cotton
- 13 April 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  receipt from John Holmes to John N. Tazewell for payment for plastering at dwelling house on Granby Street
- 17 April 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  Anne E. Bradford to Sally Tazewell-son home from school, husband gone for now-concerned but things are quiet-trying to plant a garden-things confused-negative photostat
- 23 April 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  Anne E. Bradford to Sally Tazewell-sends a copy of Lee's surrender order-discusses surrender-news of friends-transcript of Lee's order-negative photostat
- May 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  Anne E. Bradford to Sally Tazewell-all didn't think fall of Richmond a serious blow to Confederacy-but Lee's surrender was-Jefferson Davis' address-Davis a fugitive-hopes things come to quick resolution-blacks getting "unruly"-copy of Davis' address on withdrawal of government from Richmond-negative photostat
- 6 May 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  receipt from DeCordy, lumber merchant, Norfolk to C. Gordon-paid
- 11 May 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  Anne E. Bradford to Sally Tazewell-Edmund going to Danville for a parole-will go to Norfolk and check things out-two daughters will go with him-things o.k. whole family will return-post war changes-one servant took off-doubts Edmund will get the pass he needs-12 May 1865-Edmund Bradford to Sally Tazewell-received pass and will be coming to Norfolk-negative photostat
- 12 May 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  parole of Edmund Bradford-quartermaster general and inspector of tax in kind-pass allowing him to go home to Norfolk-negative photostat
- 18 May 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  receipt from George L. Crow to Miss Tazewell for payment for repairs to pump
- 19 May 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  receipt from B. W. Gatch to Sally Tazewell for payment for painting porch floor and cornice
- 23 May 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  receipt from A. L. Saeabury to Sally Tazewell for payment for ladies gaiters
- 25 May 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  receipt from S. G. Tuttle to Miss Tazewell for payment for ice cream
- 8 June 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  receipt from Charles Doyle to John N. Tazewell for payment for butter
- 12 June 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  receipt from M. Forman to [Tazewell?] Taylor for payment for cord of wood and drayage
- 17 June 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  Anne E. Bradford to unknown recipient [probably Captain O. Brown]-regarding her farm in Princess Anne County currently under control of this person as superintendent of Negro Affairs-wants that part of property that is supposed to be returned to her
- 18 June 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- 19 June 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  copy of the above letter-includes a notarized statement
- 19 June 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  Anne E. Bradford to Major Hudson, collector of customs-her house at 70 at west end of Main Street-left Norfolk in 1862 to be with an ill child in Raleigh-General Dix said go, but don't come back during war-had someone in the house for her-that person was told to get out in January 1864 and the house was taken over by the government-would like it back
- 20 June 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  receipt from Norfolk post office for payment for newspaper postage-Mrs. M. P. Waller
- 22 June 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  receipt with Banking House of Samuel Harris and Sons
- 24 June 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  city tax for Norfolk-John, Sally, and Ella Tazewell
- 24 June 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  city tax for Norfolk-Mary P. Waller
- 24 June 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  city tax for Norfolk-Sally Tazewell
- 26 June 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  United States Internal Revenue-excise tax on income in Northampton County-Sally Tazewell
- 26 June 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  United States Internal Revenue-excise tax on income in Northampton County-Ella Tazewell
- 26 June 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  United States Internal Revenue-excise tax on gold watch, silver-Ella Tazewell
- 26 June 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  United States Internal Revenue-excise tax on silver plate-Mrs. M. P. Waller
- 26 June 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  United States Internal Revenue-excise tax on silver-John N. Tazewell
- 26 June 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  United States Internal Revenue-excise tax on gold watch-Sally Tazewell
- 26 June 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  United States Internal Revenue-excise tax on income in Northampton County-John N. Tazewell
- 28 June 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  endorsement (copy)-order to turn over Bradford fishery to Mrs. A. E. Bradford-must lease it to occupant on same terms
- 28 June 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  Department of Negro Affairs-Bradford Fishery to be turned over to Mrs. Bradford-freedmen to be left alone on farm
- 30 June 1865 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  receipt for pew rent to Misses Tazewell-pew at Christ Church
- 1865 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  list of documents for Anne Bradford's petition to reclaim her property
- 1865 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  envelope addressed to John N. Tazewell probably from John C. Wise
- 4 or 11 October 1865 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  account Sally Tazewell to Robert B. Tunstall-medical visits-paid
- 5 July 1865 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  receipt-Kimberly Brothers to Sally Tazewell-candles-paid
- 8 July 1865 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  receipt from William Grieve to John N. Tazewell for payment for coat and pants tailoring
- 11 July 1865 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  receipt from Mervin and Ferguson for butter
- 20 July 1865 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  receipt from John D. Brown to Ella Tazewell for payment for building cistern
- 21 July 1865 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  receipt-account of John N. Tazewell with Lockhart and Stiner dealers in Ladies' and Gent's furnishing and toilet articles-shirt-paid
- 22 July 1865 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  receipt from M. A. Norris to Sally Tazewell for payment for Miss Nannie's dress
- 22 July 1865 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  receipt-account of Miss Tazewell with William B. Tyson-pickled salmon-paid
- 27 July 1865 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  receipt from Jupiter White for cord of wood and hauling
- 3 August 1865 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  notes from Freedmen's Bureau regarding Bradfords' Princess Anne County property occupied by freedmen
- 12 August 1865 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  United States Internal Revenue-William Lambert-excise tax on 1864 income and carriage
- 12 August 1865 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  account of John N. Tazewell with Robert B. Tunstall-medical visits-paid
- 14 August 1865 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  receipt-A. A. McCullough, coal lumber for materials-Sally Tazewell
- 16 August 1865 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  receipt-E. P. Tabb and Co.-nails, hooks, locket-Sally Tazewell-paid
- 17 August 1865 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  receipt-E. P. Tabb and Co.-screws[?], hooks-Sally Tazewell-paid
- 18 August 1865 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  receipt-G. Barnes-sash, shutters-Sally Tazewell-paid
- 18 August 1865 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  Edmund Bradford to Captain A. S. Flagg, Fort Monroe-fishery belonging to Anne Bradford returned-freedmen's bureau rented it to man named Cook-Cook supposed to pay Bradford rent-actually paid the Bureau-asks money be returned to his wife
- 19 August 1865 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  receipt-E. P. Tabb and Co.-nails-Sally Tazewell-paid
- 24 August 1865 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- 26 August 1865 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- 28 August 1865 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  Charles E. Johnston assistant superintendent of the Bureau refugees, freedmen, and abandoned lands to Mr. Cook-not fulfilled his lease conditions-must pay all monies due or lease will be taken away
- 29 August 1865 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  receipt-E. P. Tabb and Co.-screws-Sally Tazewell-paid
- 30 August 1865 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  petition of Anne E. Bradford and Edmund Bradford to the superintendent of the Bureau of Refugees, Freedmen, and abandoned lands-house in Norfolk and farm in Princess Anne County-wants property back-not engaged in action against the United States-reasons why she left Norfolk-property not abandoned-given to trustee-notarized
- 30 August 1865 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  receipt-E. P. Tabb and Co.-draw pully, hinge and screws-Sally Tazewell-paid
- 31 August 1865 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- 1 September 1865 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  receipt-E. P. Tabb and Co.-draw pully-Sally Tazewell-paid
- 1 September 1865 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- 2 September 1865 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  petition for pardon from Edmund Bradford to Andrew Johnson, President of the United States-reviews his military career-states he took both oaths required-finds he falls into one of the categories for exceptions and therefore petitions for a pardon by the president-negative photostat
- 2 September 1865 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  receipt-E. P. Tabb and Co.-draw pully, hinge and screws-Sally Box Tazewell-paid
- 16 September 1865 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  Edmund Bradford-certifies that neither his wife or her trustee (Sally Tazewell) fall within the exceptions mentioned by President Johnson-that property they want restored given to his wife by her father LWT and not worth more than $15000
- 16 September 1865 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  John C. Wise of Princess Anne County to John N. Tazewell-asks for Tazewell's advice for his son who wants to become a lawyer
- 21 September 1865 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  repairing brick work by B. Frank Bolsom-account and receipt paid by John N. Tazewell
- 22 September 1865 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  receipt-Santos and Brother-coal-Sally Tazewell-paid
- 23 September 1865 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- 23 September 1865 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- 26 September 1865 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  receipt from Griffin Barnes for payment for door blinds and drayage-Sally Tazewell
- 26 September 1865 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  account of Miss Tazewell with Charles A. Smith-linen, flannel, etc-paid
- 28 September 1865 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  certified by W. H. Barry-no proceedings for confiscation of property of Anne Bradford had been commenced in the United States District Court, District of Virginia
- 30 September 1865 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  receipt for cord of wood and drayage from Jupiter White
- 2 October 1865 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  receipt from City Gas Works Norfolk, VA. to John N. Tazewell-payment for gas
- 13 October 1865 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  state tax, city of Norfolk-Sally Tazewell
- 13 October 1865 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  state tax, city of Norfolk-Sally, Ella, [and John?] Tazewell
- 13 October 1865 (Box 9, Folder 12)